http://www.thebrunswicknews.com/site/privacy.html

Brunswick, GA
(31520)
Today
Plentiful sunshine. High 69F. Winds S at 5 to 10 mph..
Tonight
A few clouds. Low 49F. Winds light and variable.
Medical Directory 2019
This Privacy Policy was last modified on March 23, 2018.The Brunswick News ("us", "we", or "our") operates http://www.thebrunswicknews.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.Information Collection And UseWhile using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").Log DataLike many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Third-Party AdsWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. Data may be collected in order to display ads that include goods and services of interest to you. This data includes your browser’s activities such as the types of pages you visit and your categories of interest. This data does not personally identify you.If you wish to opt-out of interest-based third-party advertising you may use the opt-out tool provided by the Network Advertising Initiative at http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/. If you would like more information about the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads on our website please contact us.Changes To This Privacy PolicyThe Brunswick News may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Latest News
Local media reports Hong Kong media tycoon Jimmy Lai has been charged under national security law
Sen. Rand Paul delays defense bill vote over troop drawdowns
Congress stuck, McConnell resists state aid in COVID-19 deal
In Arizona, Trump's false claims have torn open a GOP rift
California's health order falling on many deaf ears
Most Popular
Articles
ArticlesLocal businessman opens eighth restaurantCops: Man stable after shooting in BrunswickGrand jury indicts hunter in teen's shooting deathCutting along dotted lines could speed up salvageDeveloper eyes island's north end for commercial ventureSupreme Court denies mass killer's appealChristmas lights tradition goes on after resident's deathShipwreck update: Preparations for next cut continue, COVID-19 reappearsTiny home groundbreaking heldTexas suing Georgia, three other states over handling of presidential election
Latest e-Edition
The Brunswick News
To view our latest e-Edition click the image on the left.
© Copyright 2019 Brunswick News Publishing Co. | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
